[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country did Raclette cheese originate?", "correct_answer": "Switzerland", "incorrect_answers": ["Spain", "Italy", "France"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When the player \u201csurrenders\u201d in Blackjack, what part of his/her bet does he/she lose?", "correct_answer": "One half", "incorrect_answers": ["One fifth", "The whole bet", "Two thirds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Law of Inertia is also referred to as this.", "correct_answer": "Newtons First Law", "incorrect_answers": ["Newtons Third Law", "Fundamental law of dynamics", "Newtons Second Law"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the The Fellowship of the Ring movie, what is the name of Sams crush?", "correct_answer": "Rosie", "incorrect_answers": ["Sally", "Suzie", "Rubby"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ray Milland was nominated for an Oscar for his role in the 1972 movie The Thing with Two Heads.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This famous American writer wrote all of the novel Cannery Row in pencil. He claimed to have used 60 pencils a day for his writings.", "correct_answer": "John Steinbeck", "incorrect_answers": ["Henry David Thoreau", "Ernest Hemingway", "Nathaniel Hawthorne"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the characters in the 2006 film The Benchwarmers is portrayed by Rob Shneider?", "correct_answer": "Gus", "incorrect_answers": ["Tony", "Carl", "Phil"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the communications specialist of Megatron in Transformers 2?", "correct_answer": "Soundwave", "incorrect_answers": ["Pulsar", "Echo", "Phonon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jog Falls is the highest plunge waterfall in this Asian country.", "correct_answer": "India", "incorrect_answers": ["Japan", "China", "Thailand"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This duo was formed by Roland Orzabel and Curt Smith in the early 1980s. Their songs Shout and Everybody Wants to Rule the World both hit #1on the US Pop Charts.", "correct_answer": "Tears for Fears", "incorrect_answers": ["Dire Straits", "Graduate", "Air Supply"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to Greek mythology, he was the best friend of Pythias.", "correct_answer": "Damion", "incorrect_answers": ["Daconias", "Draco", "Desmond"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This type of Belgian beer contains alcohol by volume, ranging between 8 an 11 percent. A commercial example for this kind of beer is Unibroue la Fin du Monde.", "correct_answer": "tripel", "incorrect_answers": ["aetbier", "uerige", "dunkel"]}]